That one, I'm getting even more confused.
That one from Yumiri didn't look like, oh, I don't know, a poof, a house-style.
The soup was pretty much like soy sauce ramen, wasn't it?
Then, the live delivery came in, so let's keep up the good work this week.
Yes, please do.
Wow.
Yes, sir.
I'm a little nervous. I hear it's different from recording.
What we do isn't much different, but...
Oh!
Yes!
What the hell?
Don't film me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
And now, without further ado...
Thank you very much for the live broadcast.
Thank you very much.
I'm Imara Iyakata, and I'll be your regular guest starting this week.
You can call me "yellow-green idiot" if you like.
I can't afford to spend a low salary for the rest of the year, so I'll just say "hello".
I'm not sure if it's the same one I heard yesterday, or if it's just a bad one.
I'm sure you're watching the live broadcast because you're here for the first time, so how are you doing?
I'm so glad you guys made me feel so relaxed.
I'm not saying that your comment is half right and half wrong... but mainly mine...
I'm not saying I'm wrong, but it's mainly me...
I don't know how to say it... they look a little like a blonde teacher.
Blonde sensei, Blonde sensei, they talk and chew a little, their style is also similar.
Both of them are clunky, clunky, clunky, clunky, four letters each, so they're like Mr. Pon and Mr. Kotsusan this week.
Pon san and Kotsu san Pon san and Kotsu san... and the two of them together are Ponkotsu Ponkotsu...
Pon-san and Kotsun-san. Pon-san and Kotsun-san.
I'm glad to be here... and you know... from our point of view, you seem to be familiar with us.
I was a little nervous right after I first came here.
That was the first time.
After that, it's as if I've been here for years. You're so at ease.
I'm too calm...
Well, let's get on with the recording.
I've already had the opportunity to draw a picture for this show.
This is the last picture you drew of the creature on the other side.
And you, Mr. Kotto, you drew me and my teacher... and we're covered in hands.
Please don't be offended by my comment.
Why are there so many creatures, like cats?
If you ask me to draw a cat, well, it's easy, isn't it?
I can imagine it. By the way, I think cats are one of the most familiar creatures to us.
Yes, and the other one is a dog, isn't it?
By the way, are you a cat person or a dog person?
I'm a cat person, then... a cat person.
Thank you for drawing it.
This is a little too easy, isn't it?
No, no, no, I've always drawn cats.
Wait a minute! I feel it's too hard!
It's very similar. If you say it's a cat, it's hard to make people think it's not a cat, for example.
That's for sure.
Okay, first of all, let's call Master the cat, right?
Okay, then, let's start with the cat, shall we?
You know, you're a cute cat.
I just have one question... what are these balloons under here?
The tail is a simplified version. Catchy and easy to understand.
It's catchy and easy to understand.
Oh, wow!
And you made such a Fornet.
It's only the tip of the dog.
It's hard to tell which is the tip.
I can't tell which is the tip.
It looks like an eye.
Or it looks like a dog.
I don't know which way to look at it, but it looks like an eye or a dog or something.
I see. I often say that when I see a bad guy.
I've got no choice but to set him up as a genius.
But you're right, geniuses are always a surprise to the general public.
From an ordinary person's point of view.
This is like the very basics of living creature creation.
Shall we do it? Full-fledged creature creation?
Please do.
Thank you very much.
As always, the Indian music played by the Indians is wonderful.
And now... our guest from Atsugi, the witch.
May I have the creature?
Melissa!
Melissa! There's a creature called Melissa.
This, by the way, is... Melissa?
It's Greek. Greek.
There's a creature called Melissa in Greek. It's one of the most difficult names in all of history.
Is it really here? Yes, there really is one.
I'm sorry, but to the Greeks, it's like, "What the hell are you guys talking about?
Yes, I know.
In this case, it would be better to have each of you be Greek now.
Yes. What is Greece?
What do you mean when you say "Greece"?
It's a feeling of abandonment, isn't it?
I think it's probably India.
From our point of view, Greece and India are in the same direction. Greece is the birthplace of the Olympics, right?
Like Olympia? Greek mythology!
Like Olympus? Yes, like Olympus.
Did you finish it already? Yes, it's ready! Okay, let's start with you, Master, Melissa, please.
Melissa, this way!
What's that? What's that? Is that a pose I've seen before?
I just thought it was a really nice pose, and it made me want to draw one too.
When I heard the name Melissa, I thought maybe Melissa was a donor.
I see. Like a golden retriever?
I see what you mean! It looks like an eye, too.So that's how it is! Surely this is what the eye sees.
It looks like this! This is the new trend!
It's her! It's genius that it's so popular because she only wears her neck and looks the same from both sides.
Well, you're right, Master... art begins with imitation.
Every genius artist started by looking at the paintings of others who were good.
Almost all of them are geniuses.
Melissa, please.
She exists? Downstairs! Down? Past tense?
Oh! There it is! Medusa?
It's the same at the beginning and the end, so it's almost like... it's almost like Melissa.
No, no, no, it's not the same at the end, it's Medusa.
This is Melissa from Medusa.
Maybe it's one of the Medusas? Yes! Her name is Melissa.
That's amazing! By the way, this one looks a lot like her mentor's.
Almost the same. That's me.
You're the artist who paints Medusa.
It's like you're turning to stone.
Melissa is a Greek word.
No, no, it's very simple.
It's a three-piece bowl.
You scared me. Who painted this?
Get me out! Wow! That's my girl!
I was surprised. I was surprised too.
I've been doing this for a long time, week after week.
When I draw people's faces and animals, I get better and better at it.
It's scary, but it's important to do it, and it's important to draw it.
Maybe we saw that today...
It was a really wonderful corner.
If you have any ideas for creatures you'd like to see in the future, please send them to us.
We'd like you to continue to send us more and more pictures.
Can I see your drawings now?
Medusa. Medusa.
Medusa, I mean.
It's like a path for you, Master.
Oh, no, the dead end is back.
Oh, it's the dead end! It's like...
It's like "St. Ten".
Okay, well, we'll be waiting for you.
Well, that's all for today's show.
See you all tomorrow!
Bye bye!
So, how's the live broadcast going?
And what does it say, "Mainly"?
Is it heavy?
Rhea, you're so refreshing!
He's become a refreshing character.
And, you know... your voice is refreshing. It's not like you're in a fight with me.
I mean, I hate to say it myself, but I really dislike my voice.
You have a nice voice, but it's a little bit thuggish, a little bit evil.
Somewhere in there, yes, I'm sure.
Oh!
Not "oh". You reacted quickly.
I don't know... but your voice, Mr. Lia... has a whiff of goodness to it.
It's the voice of a good person. And she's so polite.
After he says, "Pleased to meet you." That's right. He's very polite.
Now that you mention it, there's something about it.
Is your family like this? Did they teach you manners? Yes, my mother taught me that.
That's right... if your parents are like that...
Then I don't have to go in one more block.
Yes, I don't want to.
She's complaining about the trouble.
I can't understand what he's saying. He's wearing a mask, so I can't understand what he's saying.
Then I'd like to go one block.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Is this okay?
Yes, sir.
Okay, just close it up one more time.
Then I would like to go one more block.
We'll go to the show.
Five, four, three.
Did you go to a cherry blossom viewing party this year?
I've been wanting to.
You can go this year, right?
Yes, of course.
It's been a while.
It's been a while since I felt like we could all go.
But they're blooming and falling early this year.
It's early.
I don't know if we'll make it.
No, no, no, no...
Cherry blossoms have changed a lot in Japan over the years.
That's right.
Originally, cherry trees were planted by a gardener in the Edo period.
They did a lot of work on this next tree and so on.
That's why all of them are clones.
That's why they are all clones.
That's why they all bloom at the same time.
At the exact same time.
That's right.
But it's been a few hundred or two hundred years since then.
I don't know how long it's been.
Apparently, there are many clones of the tinted iyoshina all over Japan.
But they're nearing the end of their life span.
Lifespan?
Longevity?
Longevity.
So the wood inside the clones is already rotten and dangerous.
So they cut them down.
So it's like a generational shift.
What?
So, from now on, they'll bloom like they have in the past.So, from now on, it's going to bloom like it has in the past.
Like rows of cherry trees blooming in profusion like they have in the past.
We may not be able to see them in the near future.
I think I'll probably replace them with new ones.
I don't think the new one will be a clone of the old one.
So maybe they won't be able to bloom at the same time.
It will disappear.
It might disappear.
Sad.
By the way, there is a huge cherry tree in my neighborhood.
It's already this thick.
It was in full bloom.
One day, a city official came and a tree doctor was cutting down the tree.
He said that the inside of the tree was already rotten and gone.
He told me that the tree would fall over if I left it alone.
He said, "It's dangerous, so I'm going to cut it down.
Just like that, it was gone.
That's so sad.
That's right.
Instead, they planted a new, thinner one of a different kind.
It's true that the flowers come with a big bang, but...
But it's not like before...
I have a movie of that time.
Let's take a look at it.
This is a little different from the excellent dyeing.
What do you call this?
Straight!
Superior dyeing is more like this.
Yes, it's angled.
That's right.
It's much more powerful... than the excellent dye job.
Much more.
But it's almost in full bloom.
Yes, it is.
It's early this year, and maybe this kind of flower is early.
Is that so?
Compared to, say, dyed-in-the-wool varieties?
Yes.
Maybe the flower viewing season will be a little different from now on.
That's true.
It'll be more fun.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
It's me today, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's the day I've been waiting for.
April 6th
What day is it?
April 6th?
Let's just say it's the first day of the month.
Sh... yo... nice to meet you!
Hey!
Nice to meet you!
Oh, no!
I don't know...
Sh...
April 6th.
"Kimonos...
What was "Shiro-Muku" again?
Shiro-Muku is a white kimono
It's a white dress that a bride wears on her wedding day...
Wedding anniversary?
No, no, no, no.
It's like an association game.
It's true that the white kimono is worn by the bride on her wedding day.
The bride's.
Can I get the white kimono?
White...
Can I ask White to come back here once?
Building castles.
Correct!
Today is Castle Day.
Castles all over Japan.
For example, the famous Osaka Castle
Nagoya Castle, and Himeji Castle.
For example, Osaka Castle, Nagoya Castle, and Himeji Castle.
For example, Osaka Castle, Nagoya Castle, Himeji Castle, and so on.
By the way...
On top of the castle
There's a guy like this...
You see this guy?
He looks like a boy
But it looks like this...
You see...
Like this...
Little bird.
A little bird.
Chirping on the roof of the castle.
Maybe they're there.
I'm sure they're there, but...
It's on top of the castle like this.
Like this...
Like an ebizo...
Like an ebizo.
Like this...something like this
Something about gold
Nagoya.
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Shaji
Shaji...
It's like...
It's like a bang, then a bang, then a bang, then a bang.
Sha-ji Hot!
Sha-ji Hotchkiss.
It's a golden Sha-chi Hokkoh.
The Golden Shrine Hotchkiss...
Actually...
Right now...
It was built on the roofs of castles all over Japan.
The first of its kind in Japan.
What a surprise...
Azuchi Castle.
Nobunaga Oda.
That's exactly what it is.
Oh!
Right?
And the next one after that.
There are two of them.
The bosses are imaginary creatures with a tiger or dragon-like face and a fish-like body.
It's supposed to be some kind of amulet, but... well, well, well...
By the way, the castle...
If you had to decide whether you like it or not, which would it be?
If I had to choose between liking and disliking castles, I didn't like them that much when I was a kid.
But now that I'm an adult, I've come to appreciate the history of the building, and I think it's something I'll enjoy in the future.
Wait for the future?
Wait a minute. Why do you have to be so cliche about it?
I think it's something that I might enjoy in the future.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. I haven't found it appealing yet.
I'm going to repeat my question one more time. I asked you if you liked or disliked it.
I don't care about the content. You'll have to work that out for yourself.
Like it or not? Like it or not, it's just so...
Okay, that's enough. You're done.
Then, what if I like or dislike Cospro?
But I've been going to castles since I was a kid.
If I had to choose, I'd say I like it.
I liked it. Etsu Castle is pretty cool.
If I had to choose between liking and disliking it, I'd say I love it.
Castles remind you of something like that, like a building.
But Azuchi Castle was probably the first castle like that in Japan.
So the castle we imagine now was the first of its kind in Japan.
It was the first castle in Japan, and it was built in such a way that it was a waste of time and money.
I think it was the tallest building in Japan, and the first skyscraper in the history of Japan.
But right before that, they dug a hole in the mountain.
So it was more like a fortress than a building, almost like the castle of Fuun Takeichi.
But from Azuchi Castle, all of a sudden, that kind of thing started happening.
I didn't know it was Azuchi Castle.
Well, well, well, well... Let's hear from you, then.
Yes, please.
Let's see...
Yes.
Yes. Let's see, yes.
Mr. Tricoloro.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Zamashii.
Oh, this is good. Peruvian restaurant in Kawasaki Station.
Peruvian?
That's the name of the restaurant, Alcoylis.
I'll have the lomo saltado, a traditional Peruvian dish, and the rum coke.
I think rum coke is a liquor.
I had it.
By the way, you know where Peru is, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Peru.
Over there.
That way?
That way.
That way, right?
I see. In terms of direction, it's probably where it might be.
Earth is also from Alice.
That's right.
Easilycoke.
Indeed.
That way.
You know Peru.
It is already across the sea.
It is beyond the sea, isn't it?
That is really correct though.
It really is.
You know South America in the direction of Brazil and other countries in the Pacific Ocean?
It is just like that.
Japan and South America.
The ocean. Yes. If you go there, you can see the ocean.
Without the sea, it's almost like they're next door. It's far away. It's very far away, but in South America, it's facing this way. So it's over the ocean.
The master is Per. That's right. Pell is on the other side of the earth. It's like we are on the other side of the world from their point of view.
That's great. It fits. It's amazing.
I think that's the famous one. Machu Picchu and Peru, right?
I've heard of it. Machu Picchu. Yes, I have. I have heard of it. I'm sure.
Let's take a look at Machu Picchu.
Machu Picchu is a World Heritage Site.
Machu Picchu.
Per, right? It belongs to the Andean log.
Urubamba Dani. Story. Nice. sci-fi like.
Urbambadani. Such peru cuisine.Urbamba Dani. Such is the peru cuisine.
By the way, you can see it in the picture.
9 degrees.
So, it was 9 degrees Celsius.
Surprisingly, there are a lot of Japanese-Americans here, as well as Peruvians.
Surprisingly, it looks like Japanese food.
It's true, it looks like a vegetable sauce.
Subuta mane
Onions... I wonder if this is beef.
What kind of meat is it?
Is it lamb?
Looks delicious!
I heard it's very tasty and it suits the palate.
It makes me want to go to Peru!
And... Sirene from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture!
Thank you very much!
I made flyer sushi!
It's great!
Here it is!
Looks delicious!
So cute!
This is like my version of Kewpie that Sirene made for me.
I like it.
Expensive flyer sushi.
With salmon roe and shrimp.
How beautiful and spring-like.
You have to pay a lot of money to have it made.
That's true.
I don't know if they sell it very often, or if it's sold in supermarkets.
You don't get a chance to eat a pack of it.
In my family, we were cheated for a long time, and we were served hitsujimabushi, which is chirashi sushi.
They served me flyer sushi, saying it was Hitsujimabushi.
But when I went to eat real Hitsumabushi, it looked completely different.
It's a Nagoya style.
It's more like another color than this colorful with eel on it.
So I was really surprised.
We probably didn't come from a wealthy family.
Why are you confessing?
We were about to cry.
I'm sorry.
I guess I was fooled... by the sushi fliers, like it was something respectable.
I don't know if it was deception or parental kindness.
I think that the price of Chirashizushi and Hitsumabushi are not that different.
They're not different?
It's true that eel is a luxury item and some types are outrageously expensive.
Maybe that's what it is, but even chirashi sushi is not that expensive.
That's right.
But listen, there are commercially available sushi mixers that mix sushi with lotus root and bamboo shoots, right?
Yes, there is.
So it's just a yellow egg on top of what looks like rice stock.
Prohibited egg
Isn't this also very different from eel in this state?
Very different.
Certainly.
It looks much cheaper.
Indeed.
Wait a minute.
Why would the master's parents do such a terrible thing to their son?
It doesn't make sense.
I feel like there's some kind of malice in this.
I'm sorry.
Maybe that's how my parents taught me.
Yeah, well, maybe it's because my grandma and grandpa passed it down from generation to generation.
It's possible.
They might keep thinking it's flyer sushi.
That's amazing.
What kind of family is that?
Well, let's just say...
It's kind of an interesting story.
It depends on the family.
I often say that.
When you first go to elementary school...
You go to your first friend's house.
In the summer, the mother of that friend would serve me Calpis.
And when I went over there and drank it...
I drank some Calpis and thought, "Is Calpis this thick and tasty? I thought to myself.
My mom was stingy and showed me a very thin one.
There was Calpis, wasn't there?
I thought it was Calpis and believed her.
And then I told him...
He said, "My Calpis was really thin and yours was really good.
I told him, "No, no, no, we usually have thin Calpis too.
He suddenly made it thicker.
My friend came over.
"Mya"?
Isn't that your mother's cute side?
Yes, it is.
You don't have to be so obtrusive.
It's adorable.
Well, well, well.
So you're going to do a live broadcast, too?
Well, maybe a comment or two.
Oh, right.
A cute smile?
Yes.
I thought she was well bred.
Photoware.
I have a lot of people in my college, but with them...
Then there's a certain Showa era Calpis thing labor problem
So there is?
Yes, but is there a Showa era?Yes, but it's still a Showa-era, but is it still a Showa-era?
I've got the same sex clover... well, really.
I'm surprised when I go to a stranger's house.
You know...
The first time I ate cheesecake...
I ate cheesecake for the first time because my mother bought it for me.
I was eating cheesecake all the time.
I didn't usually eat cheesecake at all.
Well, well, well, well...
So, for those of you who are still here, if you have any letters, please send them to me.
I'll see you all next week.
Thank you very much for your time this week.